Within three days
pay three times the penalty
or I'll tear down your farm
Bosses
My frogs are all dead
How can I afford to pay
Raising frogs takes patience and skill
You have neither
Today's outcome was inevitable
It's not your place
to make sarcastic remarks here
How much better could your frogs be
You have frogs
Let me see
His frogs are even worse
Too low in quality
He's too embarrassed to show them
Lewes
Open the greenhouse
Let us see your frogs
Exactly
Let us see
what you've achieved this year
Okay
Then let everyone see
I don't believe Lewes
can raise anything good
Such big frogs
How is this possible
Just watch from here
You can't just enter the greenhouse
Top grade
These must weigh over 150 grams
Their bellies are round and plump
If I had known earlier
I would have signed with Boss Lewes
Why did my frogs die
while his grew so well
Lewes
Now only you can save me